bdstall.com 2011-05-07

# Check price for tour, travel, laptop, mobile, camera, game in Bangladesh: bdstall

### Privacy Notice Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy   
The Information We Collect   
Our Commitment To Data Security   
How To Access Or Correct Your Information   
How To Contact Us

### 

* * *

Our Commitment To Privacy:  

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.   

###   
The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can register to access secured features on the site. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:   

Name   
Address (optional)  
Email address   
Phone number (mandatory for stall owner)

### The Information We DONT Collect

Credit/Debit Card Information   

###   
The Way We Use Information

We do not share or trade your information with any parties. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new  services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.   

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.   

###   
Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   

###   
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by login here.... We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.   

###   
How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
